VARUN KUMAR SINGH

Digital Marketing Executive

381/7,Arjun Nagar, Gurgaon 9536727108

Mailtovarun15@gmail.com

PROFESSIONAL SUMMARY:

Analytical and data-driven SEO Specialist with 4+ years of experience in developing, implementing, and optimizing SEO strategies. Possess strong knowledge & passion for digital marketing, driving online presence, and understanding user behavior. Excited to make an invaluable contribution across multiple digital platforms to raise search engine rank performance, traffic, engagement, conversions.

AREAS OF EXPERTISE:

Real Estate Seo

✓ OnPage Seo/offpage

Ompetitor Analysis

⊘ Ahref,semrush,moz,Screaming Frog

Managing Gwmt and google Analytics

W Keyword Research & Content Analysis

⊘ Link Building & Outreach

PROFESSIONAL EXPERIENCE:

Propertyxpo Services Pvt Ltd

Digital Marketing Executive | 15 Nov, 2019 - Present

- Research and implemented technical and on-page SEO recommendations that increase organic traffic.
- Developing and Executing off-page SEO through link Building
- Stay up-to-date with industry trends to identify keywords, enhances organic revenue

Ezone Alivetech

Seo Executive | 02 oct, 2018 - 20 Oct, 2019

- Developing and implementing effective search engine optimization (SEO) strategies
- Managing offsite and onsite optimization projects and reporting on performance
- Optimize Website Content, and landing pages.
- Collect data and report of traffic, ranking and other seo aspects to leader

RELEVANT PROJECTS:

Dlfindia.co.in

Digital Marketing | 01 jan, 2020- 10 jan, 2022

Boosted rankings Of DlfIndia.co.in from page 5 to page 1 on Google, leading to the Dlfindia website becoming the most Lead Generated leads website in 2021

Emaarindia.net.in

Digital Marketing | 01 jan, 2020- 10 jan, 2022

Completed a performance analysis every 3 months to drive link-building strategies, keeping 93% of emaarinda pages in the first 3 positions on Google for 3+ years in a row

EDUCATION:

2014 - 2018 | Dr. A.P.J. Abdul Kalam Technical University

Bachelor of Computer Science - Software Engineering

SEO PORTFOLIO

Website: https://www.propertyxpo.com/(On going)

No	Targeted Keyword	Search Engine	Ranking Position(28-07-23)
1	malibu town	Google.com	8
2	aipl joy street	Google.com	5
3	dlf camellias	Google.com	4
4	tata primanti	Google.com	6
5	ambience mall gurugram	Google.com	5

Website: https://www.Tender247.com(On going)

No	Targeted Keyword	Search Engine	Ranking Position(28-07-23)
1	eproc tata steel	Google.com	4
2	fabrication tenders	Google.com	1
3	tender in Bangalore	Google.com	2
4	nhai tenders	Google.com	4
5	hal tenders	Google.com	4

Website: https://www.theclonesworld.com/

No	Targeted Keyword	Search Engine	Ranking Position(28-07-23)
1	replica watches india	Google.com	7
2	first copy watches in india	Google.com.au	5
3	imported watches first copy	Google.com.au	7

Website: https://www.mastidubai.com (ongoing)

No	Targeted Keyword	Search Engine	Ranking Position(28-07-23)
1	masti restaurant	Google.com.ae	1
2	indian restaurant	Google.com.ae	19
3	la mer restaurants	Google.com.ae	17
4	best indian food dubai	Google.com.ae	21
5	indian restaurant Dubai	Google.com.ae	21

Website: https://www.allobeirutstreetfood.com/(On going)

No	Targeted Keyword	Search Engine	Ranking Position(28-07-23)
1	allo beirut	Google.com.ae	1
2	allo beirut city walk	Google.com.ae	4
3	beirut restaurant dubai	Google.com.ae	5
4	allo beirut barsha	Google.com.ae	2
5	beirut restaurant near me	Google.com.ae	4

Website: https://aviatechnikcorp.com/ (On going)

No	Targeted Keyword	Search Engine	Ranking Position(28-07-23)
1	flyembraer	Google.com.ca	1
2	freight forwarding toronto	Google.com.ca	13
3	landing gear manufacturers	Google.com.ca	21
4	gear repair	Google.com.ca	9
5	aircraft repair	Google.com.ca	16

Website: https://cannoliqueens.com/

No	Targeted Keyword	Search Engine	Ranking Position(19-06-22)
1	cannoli queens	Google.ca	1
2	carousel cake	Google.ca	4
3	coconut cake toronto	Google.ca	6
4	decadent chocolate	Google.ca	6
5	sweet box	Google.ca	13

Website: https:/www.dlfindia.co.in/

No	Targeted Keyword	Search Engine	Ranking Position(19-06-2022
1	Maulsari Estate City Floors	Google.com	1
2	DLF PRIMUS	Google.com	4
3	DLF Skycourt	Google.com	6
4	DLF ULTIMA	Google.com	7
5	DLF The Crest	Google.com	8

Website: https://www.spazeindia.in/

No	Targeted Keyword	Search Engine	Ranking Position(19-06-22)
1	Spaze Tristaar	Google.com	4
2	Spaze Privy	Google.com	4
3	SPAZE KALISTAA	Google.com	3
4	SPAZE PRIVVYTHE ADDRESS	Google.com	4
5	spaze sco plots	Google.com	2

SEO did on Other Domains listed below:

- 1) https://emaarindia.net.in/
- 2) https://ambselfiesteet.com/
- 3) https://stuffisbest.com/
- 4) https://centralparkindia.com/
- 5) https://spazeindia.net.in/